globalsign.com 2019-12-24

# 

GlobalSign Privacy Policy Version 3.1
Updated June 5, 2018
    GlobalSign respects your right to privacy. This privacy policy has been developed to inform you
    about the privacy practices followed by GlobalSign in connection with its websites, products and
    services. This privacy policy does not apply to GlobalSign services offered by or through our
    partners, resellers or other third parties, or other third party services or websites, and we
    encourage you to read the privacy policies of those parties.
    This privacy policy will inform you about what data is collected, how we use such data, where
    data is processed, how you may opt out of your data being used, the security provisions around
    storing your data and how to correct, update or delete your data.
    1.       Data Controller
    The data controller for personal data collected within the EU is GMO GlobalSign, Ltd., having its
    registered offices at Springfield House, Sandling Road, Maidstone, Kent, ME14 2LP, United
    Kingdom. All questions or requests regarding the processing of data may be addressed
    to: dpo@globalsign.com.
    2.       Collection of Personal Information
    We collect information from you when you (i) place an order for a GlobalSign digital certificate
    product or other product or service, (ii) scan your servers for digital certificates using our
    Certificate Inventory Tool (CIT), (iii) apply for access to our managed service platforms, (iv)
    subscribe to our newsletter, (v) use our online chat service, (vi) download a white paper, (vii)
    register for a webinar, (viii) respond to a survey, (ix) fill out a form for pre/post sales assistance,
    (x) open a support ticket, or (xi) your use of social media.
    GlobalSign is a Certification Authority and trusted third party. To fulfill requests for digital
    certificates or other products or services, you may be asked to enter your name, email address,
    physical address, phone number, credit card information and/or organizational details or other
    personal information.
             -   Contact information such as your name, email address, physical address, and phone
                 number.
             -   Relationship information that helps us do business with you, such as the types of
                 products and services that may interest you, contact and product preferences,
                 languages, marketing preferences and demographic data.
             -   Transactional information about how you interact with us, including purchases,
                 inquiries, customer account information, billing and credit card information,
                 organizational details, transaction and correspondence history, and information about
                 how you use and interact with our website.
    We may develop and acquire additional information about you using third-party (public and
    private) data sources such as third party databases and government agencies, as well as your
    browsing and purchasing history in order to process orders for certificates and to improve our
    services.
    GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18                                             1 of 6

GlobalSign treats personal information as confidential, except for the information included in an
issued digital certificate. Such information may be verified using third party commercial and
government resources, and as such, is deemed to be public information.
3.       Purpose of Processing
Your personal data will be used for the purposes specified below:
3.1 To process applications for GlobalSign products and services
Your information is used to provide our products and services and order processing as well as to
conduct business transactions such as billing.
3.2 To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your pre/post sales requests and
provide technical support.
3.3 To send renewal notices
The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you renewal notices for
your expiring digital certificate.
3.4 To send service updates
In addition, subject to your consent where required, we may send you new service updates,
security updates, related product or service information, and status updates on maintenance
windows or service availability.
3.5 To tell you about our products and services
Subject to your consent where required, we may send you periodic company newsletters,
information about our products and services that may be of interest to you based on your use of
other GlobalSign products and services, your attendance at GlobalSign sponsored marketing
events such as webinars, your requests for information about similar products and services, or
your sharing of data with social media sites such as LinkedIn or Facebook.
4.       Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data
We will process your data for the purpose of performance of our contract with you or the
legitimate interest of GlobalSign, which are our usual business activities. In other cases, we will
request your consent for the processing of the personal data you may submit.
Your refusal to provide personal data to us for certain products and services may hinder us from
fulfilling your order for those products or services. Also, if you deny or withdraw your consent to
use personal data or opt out of receiving information about GlobalSign products and services this
may result in you not being made aware of renewal notices, periodic company newsletters, new
service updates, security updates, related product or service information, and status updates on
maintenance windows or service availability. See Section 10 below for how to withdraw your
consent.
5.       Use of Cookies and web beacons
The GlobalSign Certificate Center (GCC) uses cookies to enable the fulfillment of services. Cookies
may be used when you log into the GCC, purchase products or use certain GCC functions.
In addition, like most online businesses, GlobalSign uses cookies and web beacons on our
websites and through marketing related emails to gather and analyze some personal data such as
GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18                                           2 of 6

the visitor’s IP address, browser type, ISP, referring page, operating system, date/time and basic
geographical information.
We use cookies and web beacons to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction
so that we can gauge the effectiveness of our communications and offer better site experiences
and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information
collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
First time visitors may choose to not have any activity monitoring cookies set in their browser.
We use an opt-out identification cookie to tag these users as having made this decision. Those
cookies that pertain to site performance, experience improvement and marketing are
programmed not to execute when an opt-out cookie is present in a visitor’s browser. Opt-out
cookies persist until a visitor clears their browser cookies, or until their expiration one year after
the set date. A visitor is required to opt out again after one year in order to disable any activity
monitoring cookies.
More details of GlobalSign’s use of cookies can be found on our website at
https://www.globalsign.com/en/repository/cookie-policy/
6.       Use of application logs for diagnostics or to gather statistical information
Our servers automatically record information ("Application Log Data") created by your use of our
services. Application Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type,
operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and
application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We use this information to diagnose and
improve our services. Except as stated in section 8 (Data Retention), we will either delete the
Application Log Data or remove any account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or
email address, after 12 months.
7.       Sharing of Information and Transfers of Data
We do not sell or trade your personal information to outside parties.
Within GlobalSign: GlobalSign is a global organization with business processes and technical
systems in various countries. As such, we may share information about you within our group
company and transfer it to countries in the world where we do business in connection with the
uses identified in section 3 above and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In cases where
your personal data is transferred to countries that do not provide an adequate level of protection
according to the European Commission (‘adequacy decision’), we ensure your data is protected by
entering into agreements containing standard contractual clauses approved by the European
Commission with each of our group companies. A copy of these agreements may be obtained by
contacting us as outlined in section 15 below..
Third Parties: We may also transfer your personal data to trusted third parties and our partners
in order to serve purposes that are specified in section 3 above. GlobalSign uses a third party to
process credit card payments and provides credit card numbers and identifying financial data
directly to the third party credit card processor.
In circumstances where data is shared with such third parties, they are required to comply with
confidentiality terms included in our data processing agreements. This prohibits such third
parties from selling, trading, using, marketing or otherwise distributing GlobalSign customer data.
GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18                                             3 of 6

As Required by Law: We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law or protect our rights, property, or safety.
It is our policy to notify customers of requests for their data from law enforcement unless we are
prohibited from doing so by statute or court order. Law enforcement officials who believe that
notification would jeopardize an investigation should obtain an appropriate court order or other
process that specifically precludes member notification, such as an order issued pursuant to 18
U.S.C. §2705(b).
Mergers & Acquisitions: We may also disclose your personal information to third parties who may
take over the operation of our site or who may purchase any or all of our assets, including your
personal information. We will contact you using the details you provide if there is any change in
the person controlling your information.
8.       International Transfers
The third parties, subsidiaries and affiliates to which your personal information can be disclosed
may be located throughout the world. Therefore, information may be sent to countries having
different privacy protection standards than your country of residence. In such cases, we take
measures to ensure that your personal information receives an adequate level of protection,
which includes the EU Standard Contractual Clauses to protect your personal information.
9.       Data retention
The personal information we collect is retained for no longer than necessary to fulfil the stated
purposes in section 2 above or for a period specifically required by law or regulation that
GlobalSign is obligated to follow.
To meet public CA audit requirements as detailed in the GlobalSign Certification Practice
Statement, personal data used to fulfill verification of certain types of digital certificate
applications will be retained for a minimum of 10 years depending on the class of product or
service and may be retained in either a physical or electronic format. Please refer to the
GlobalSign Certification Practice Statement for full details.
After the retention period is over, GlobalSign securely disposes or anonymizes your personal
information in order to prevent loss, theft, misuse, or unauthorized access.
10.      Opting out; withdrawing consent
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe
instructions at the bottom of each email.
Renewal notices may be cancelled on a per digital certificate basis by logging into your GlobalSign
Certificate Center (GCC) account and disabling renewal notices.
Email preferences for CIT related/collected information can be updated and changed within CIT.
If GlobalSign is processing your personal data based on your consent, you may withdraw your
consent at any time via the GlobalSign Preference Centre at
https://downloads.globalsign.com/acton/media/2674/preference-center-login or by contacting
us at one of the addresses shown in section 15 below.
11.      Your Rights
GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18                                              4 of 6

You are responsible for providing GlobalSign with true, accurate, current and complete personal
information. Also, you are responsible to maintain and promptly update the information to keep it
true, accurate, current and complete.
You have the right to access and modify your personal data stored on GlobalSign systems.
You can exercise your rights by contacting us in writing. We will require you to provide
identification in order to verify the authenticity as the data subject. We will make reasonable
efforts to respond to and process your request as required by law.
To the extent of applicable law, you may have the right to request erasure of your personal
information, restriction of processing as it applies to you, object to processing and the right to
data portability. You may also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or if we have
reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or
incomplete, we have the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current
or future services.
12.      How we protect your information
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information
when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. All supplied
sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL).
After a transaction, your transaction-related information will be kept on file to meet audit
requirements and facilitate renewals. We do not retain any credit card details.
13.      Relevant laws
GlobalSign commits itself to protect the personal information submitted by applicants and
subscribers for its public certification services. GlobalSign declares to fully respect all rights
established and laid out in European Union and Member States’ laws and regulations:
        European Directive 95/46 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing
         of personal data and on the free movement of such data and as replaced by Regulation EU
         2016/679 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal
         data and on the free movement of such data (the EU General Data Protection Regulation);
         and
        Provisions of the GlobalSign CPS.
14.      Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we make material changes to our privacy policy, we will inform customers by emailing a notice
of the availability of a new version with a link to the new version.
15.      Contact Us
If you have any inquires, or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
https://support.globalsign.com/
https://www.globalsign.com/en/company/contact/support/
https://jp.globalsign.com/support/
or
GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18                                              5 of 6

Deputy Data Protection Officer
GMO GlobalSign, Ltd.
Springfield House Sandling Road
Maidstone, Kent ME 14 2LP
United Kingdom
dpo@globalsign.com
16.     Our Office Locations
GMO GlobalSign K.K., Tokyo, Japan
GMO GlobalSign Ltd., Maidstone, Kent, UK
GMO GlobalSign N/V, Leuven, Belgium
GMO GlobalSign, Inc., Portsmouth, NH, USA
GMO GlobalSign Russia LLC , Moskva, Russia
GMO GlobalSign Pte. Ltd, Anson, Singapore
GMO GlobalSign Certificate Services Pvt. Ltd., Delhi, India
GlobalSign China Co., Ltd., Shanghai, China
GMO GlobalSign Inc., Manila, Philippines
GMO GlobalSign FZ-LLC, Dubai, UAE
GlobalSign Privacy Policy - Version 3 1 6-5-18              6 of 6
